IPL Cricket Analytics Dashboard
Built with Microsoft Power BI
Covering 15 seasons of IPL | 2008 – 2022
950 matches | 296,000 runs | All in one report
3 interactive pages | Explore. Filter. Discover.
Loading IPL Analytics...
IPL Championship Trends | 2008 – 2022
Mumbai Indians — Most titles | Highest win rate
Toss winners choose to field 60%+ of the time
Home advantage is real — home teams win significantly more
Interactive slicers — filter by team, season & venue
Season Spotlight: IPL 2017
Mumbai Indians — IPL 2017 Champions
DA Warner | 641 runs | Top scorer of the season
B Kumar | 26 wickets | Leading wicket-taker in 2017
Drill-through filters for match-level insights
Team & Player Performance Explorer
Compare any team across all 15 seasons
Built using DAX | Power Query | Data Modeling
My first Power BI project — built from scratch
Trained at Luminar Technolab | Guided by Rakesh O V Sir